{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803318989","data":{"timestamp":" 946803318989"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803323574","data":{"timestamp":" 946803323574"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803346673","data":{"timestamp":" 946803346673"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803351866","data":{"timestamp":" 946803351866"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803354966","data":{"timestamp":" 946803354966"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803358436","data":{"timestamp":" 946803358436"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803361261","data":{"timestamp":" 946803361261"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803366437","data":{"timestamp":" 946803366437"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803369670","data":{"timestamp":" 946803369670"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803373381","data":{"timestamp":" 946803373381"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803376897","data":{"timestamp":" 946803376897"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803380298","data":{"timestamp":" 946803380297"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803388771","data":{"timestamp":" 946803388771"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803393049","data":{"timestamp":" 946803393049"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803398827","data":{"timestamp":" 946803398827"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803404055","data":{"timestamp":" 946803404054"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803406655","data":{"timestamp":" 946803406655"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803410198","data":{"timestamp":" 946803410198"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803423542","data":{"timestamp":" 946803423541"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803429212","data":{"timestamp":" 946803429212"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803436516","data":{"timestamp":" 946803436516"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803441977","data":{"timestamp":" 946803441977"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803451846","data":{"timestamp":" 946803451845"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803458937","data":{"timestamp":" 946803458936"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 565bbebf-301a-4791-abb1-8abe45c5b9fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803483325","data":{"timestamp":" 946803483325"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803490668","data":{"timestamp":" 946803490668"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803494212","data":{"timestamp":" 946803494212"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803496594","data":{"timestamp":" 946803496594"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803498768","data":{"timestamp":" 946803498768"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803503658","data":{"timestamp":" 946803503658"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803506270","data":{"timestamp":" 946803506270"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803508942","data":{"timestamp":" 946803508942"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803515857","data":{"timestamp":" 946803515857"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803520293","data":{"timestamp":" 946803520293"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803524164","data":{"timestamp":" 946803524164"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803526834","data":{"timestamp":" 946803526834"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803532047","data":{"timestamp":" 946803532046"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803542325","data":{"timestamp":" 946803542325"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803552568","data":{"timestamp":" 946803552567"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803558642","data":{"timestamp":" 946803558641"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803568293","data":{"timestamp":" 946803568293"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803578553","data":{"timestamp":" 946803578553"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803586285","data":{"timestamp":" 946803586285"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803593028","data":{"timestamp":" 946803593028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803598190","data":{"timestamp":" 946803598190"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803608366","data":{"timestamp":" 946803608366"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803611148","data":{"timestamp":" 946803611148"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803614704","data":{"timestamp":" 946803614704"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803617619","data":{"timestamp":" 946803617619"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803620717","data":{"timestamp":" 946803620717"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803625879","data":{"timestamp":" 946803625879"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803628714","data":{"timestamp":" 946803628714"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803633904","data":{"timestamp":" 946803633904"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803643221","data":{"timestamp":" 946803643221"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803649921","data":{"timestamp":" 946803649921"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803652707","data":{"timestamp":" 946803652707"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803654508","data":{"timestamp":" 946803654508"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 24"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803656438","data":{"timestamp":" 946803656437"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803669822","data":{"timestamp":" 946803669822"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803674590","data":{"timestamp":" 946803674590"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803682683","data":{"timestamp":" 946803682683"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803688240","data":{"timestamp":" 946803688240"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::herufi_kubwa","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803695133","data":{"timestamp":" 946803695133"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 175d1e93-bf27-4b46-82b8-9b4e1f0a5dc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803704408","data":{"timestamp":" 946803704408"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803704635","data":{"timestamp":" 946803704635"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803705615","data":{"timestamp":" 946803705615"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803706904","data":{"timestamp":" 946803706903"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803707548","data":{"timestamp":" 946803707547"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803707626","data":{"timestamp":" 946803707626"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803715625","data":{"timestamp":" 946803715624"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803722265","data":{"timestamp":" 946803722265"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803729917","data":{"timestamp":" 946803729917"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803738070","data":{"timestamp":" 946803738070"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9fd3d28a-0ff6-413e-b45f-6fb276e81c24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803750497","data":{"timestamp":" 946803750496"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" ff741843-aeff-4ce2-826f-b99ed072a24d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803760795","data":{"timestamp":" 946803760794"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" ff741843-aeff-4ce2-826f-b99ed072a24d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803760897","data":{"timestamp":" 946803760896"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" ff741843-aeff-4ce2-826f-b99ed072a24d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803766726","data":{"timestamp":" 946803766726"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" ef823712-2224-4e81-9bdb-05e6314e9a7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803766928","data":{"timestamp":" 946803766927"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" ef823712-2224-4e81-9bdb-05e6314e9a7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803767026","data":{"timestamp":" 946803767026"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" ef823712-2224-4e81-9bdb-05e6314e9a7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803779374","data":{"timestamp":" 946803779374"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 2c43acc9-13e6-4fe7-b118-2f5f68c85485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jembe lake lilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803782229","data":{"timestamp":" 946803782229"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 2c43acc9-13e6-4fe7-b118-2f5f68c85485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jembe lake lilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803782339","data":{"timestamp":" 946803782339"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 2c43acc9-13e6-4fe7-b118-2f5f68c85485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jembe lake lilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803792184","data":{"timestamp":" 946803792184"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dabf1387-45ae-4096-93b2-e0b9b68d24cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803792302","data":{"timestamp":" 946803792302"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dabf1387-45ae-4096-93b2-e0b9b68d24cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803792394","data":{"timestamp":" 946803792394"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dabf1387-45ae-4096-93b2-e0b9b68d24cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803820765","data":{"timestamp":" 946803820765"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803823227","data":{"timestamp":" 946803823227"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803823436","data":{"timestamp":" 946803823436"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803824172","data":{"timestamp":" 946803824171"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803826986","data":{"timestamp":" 946803826985"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEKA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803827731","data":{"timestamp":" 946803827731"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NUKTA"," userResponse":" NUKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803828536","data":{"timestamp":" 946803828535"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803828710","data":{"timestamp":" 946803828710"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803829629","data":{"timestamp":" 946803829629"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SENTENSI"," userResponse":" SENTENSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803831665","data":{"timestamp":" 946803831663"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803832339","data":{"timestamp":" 946803832338"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFANO"," userResponse":" MFANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803834890","data":{"timestamp":" 946803834889"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803835272","data":{"timestamp":" 946803835271"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803836309","data":{"timestamp":" 946803836308"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROBOTUTOR"," userResponse":" ROBOTUTOR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803838981","data":{"timestamp":" 946803838981"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803839075","data":{"timestamp":" 946803839074"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROBOTUTOR"," userResponse":" ROBOTUTOR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803845867","data":{"timestamp":" 946803845867"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" f71a97af-2c44-45b9-b3a7-efb757e8bab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803855823","data":{"timestamp":" 946803855823"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 441f3cc3-da8b-4a25-bd98-6da324d7c461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803864524","data":{"timestamp":" 946803864523"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 441f3cc3-da8b-4a25-bd98-6da324d7c461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803864630","data":{"timestamp":" 946803864630"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 441f3cc3-da8b-4a25-bd98-6da324d7c461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803887194","data":{"timestamp":" 946803887194"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 441f3cc3-da8b-4a25-bd98-6da324d7c461"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803898345","data":{"timestamp":" 946803898344"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803899814","data":{"timestamp":" 946803899814"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803902221","data":{"timestamp":" 946803902220"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803911882","data":{"timestamp":" 946803911882"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803911885","data":{"timestamp":" 946803911885"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803918526","data":{"timestamp":" 946803918526"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803920291","data":{"timestamp":" 946803920291"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803921901","data":{"timestamp":" 946803921900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803923315","data":{"timestamp":" 946803923314"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803924047","data":{"timestamp":" 946803924047"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" START_ANARUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803924583","data":{"timestamp":" 946803924582"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803924677","data":{"timestamp":" 946803924677"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" START_ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803950644","data":{"timestamp":" 946803950644"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 7d68f49a-4d7a-4d73-8130-136a1d70c907"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803960366","data":{"timestamp":" 946803960365"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803961617","data":{"timestamp":" 946803961616"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803965670","data":{"timestamp":" 946803965670"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803974751","data":{"timestamp":" 946803974751"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" MKONGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803975978","data":{"timestamp":" 946803975978"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803977779","data":{"timestamp":" 946803977778"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803979689","data":{"timestamp":" 946803979689"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803981766","data":{"timestamp":" 946803981766"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803983510","data":{"timestamp":" 946803983510"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803985792","data":{"timestamp":" 946803985791"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803990965","data":{"timestamp":" 946803990965"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803993439","data":{"timestamp":" 946803993438"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" START_TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803996584","data":{"timestamp":" 946803996584"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803998180","data":{"timestamp":" 946803998179"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803999360","data":{"timestamp":" 946803999360"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804001132","data":{"timestamp":" 946804001132"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804002562","data":{"timestamp":" 946804002562"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804005128","data":{"timestamp":" 946804005128"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804006848","data":{"timestamp":" 946804006848"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804008363","data":{"timestamp":" 946804008363"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804012065","data":{"timestamp":" 946804012065"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804013608","data":{"timestamp":" 946804013608"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804014863","data":{"timestamp":" 946804014863"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804014980","data":{"timestamp":" 946804014980"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_LILIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804016319","data":{"timestamp":" 946804016319"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804018044","data":{"timestamp":" 946804018043"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804020100","data":{"timestamp":" 946804020099"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804021728","data":{"timestamp":" 946804021727"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804025095","data":{"timestamp":" 946804025095"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804029887","data":{"timestamp":" 946804029887"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804031683","data":{"timestamp":" 946804031683"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804033597","data":{"timestamp":" 946804033596"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804040827","data":{"timestamp":" 946804040827"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOWEKWA"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804042730","data":{"timestamp":" 946804042730"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOWEKWA"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804044687","data":{"timestamp":" 946804044687"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOWEKWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804045446","data":{"timestamp":" 946804045446"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804046955","data":{"timestamp":" 946804046955"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804047036","data":{"timestamp":" 946804047036"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 480cb70d-4657-45d5-a7a9-61566de92cc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804055593","data":{"timestamp":" 946804055593"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804055823","data":{"timestamp":" 946804055823"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804056798","data":{"timestamp":" 946804056798"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804058092","data":{"timestamp":" 946804058092"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804061059","data":{"timestamp":" 946804061059"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804061912","data":{"timestamp":" 946804061912"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804062232","data":{"timestamp":" 946804062231"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804063479","data":{"timestamp":" 946804063479"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804067127","data":{"timestamp":" 946804067127"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804068124","data":{"timestamp":" 946804068122"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804068386","data":{"timestamp":" 946804068386"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804069340","data":{"timestamp":" 946804069340"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804072273","data":{"timestamp":" 946804072273"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804073306","data":{"timestamp":" 946804073306"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804073779","data":{"timestamp":" 946804073779"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804078431","data":{"timestamp":" 946804078430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804078514","data":{"timestamp":" 946804078511"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 499c17c0-4882-4d12-ac37-8b1964e24b52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804104255","data":{"timestamp":" 946804104255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804105907","data":{"timestamp":" 946804105907"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804110156","data":{"timestamp":" 946804110155"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804117746","data":{"timestamp":" 946804117746"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804118491","data":{"timestamp":" 946804118491"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804120244","data":{"timestamp":" 946804120243"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" START_MLINZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804122703","data":{"timestamp":" 946804122703"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804124466","data":{"timestamp":" 946804124466"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804125733","data":{"timestamp":" 946804125733"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804125736","data":{"timestamp":" 946804125736"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804127046","data":{"timestamp":" 946804127046"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804129823","data":{"timestamp":" 946804129822"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804130227","data":{"timestamp":" 946804130226"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804134748","data":{"timestamp":" 946804134748"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804135708","data":{"timestamp":" 946804135708"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804137290","data":{"timestamp":" 946804137290"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804140737","data":{"timestamp":" 946804140737"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFIKA"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804143330","data":{"timestamp":" 946804143330"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804144473","data":{"timestamp":" 946804144473"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804145824","data":{"timestamp":" 946804145824"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804147864","data":{"timestamp":" 946804147864"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804151719","data":{"timestamp":" 946804151719"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804152891","data":{"timestamp":" 946804152891"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804155164","data":{"timestamp":" 946804155164"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804156966","data":{"timestamp":" 946804156966"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804157736","data":{"timestamp":" 946804157736"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804158694","data":{"timestamp":" 946804158694"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804159050","data":{"timestamp":" 946804159049"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804159053","data":{"timestamp":" 946804159053"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804164858","data":{"timestamp":" 946804164858"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKA"," userResponse":" MWAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804164965","data":{"timestamp":" 946804164965"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804165920","data":{"timestamp":" 946804165920"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804167306","data":{"timestamp":" 946804167306"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804169396","data":{"timestamp":" 946804169396"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEBEBWA"," userResponse":" START_AMEBEBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804170429","data":{"timestamp":" 946804170429"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEBEBWA"," userResponse":" START_AMEBEBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804170457","data":{"timestamp":" 946804170457"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEBEBWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804172652","data":{"timestamp":" 946804172652"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804175796","data":{"timestamp":" 946804175796"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804177581","data":{"timestamp":" 946804177581"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804178343","data":{"timestamp":" 946804178343"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804181486","data":{"timestamp":" 946804181486"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" AMEBEBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804183057","data":{"timestamp":" 946804183056"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804184539","data":{"timestamp":" 946804184539"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804187477","data":{"timestamp":" 946804187477"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804189488","data":{"timestamp":" 946804189487"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" AMEBEBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804191399","data":{"timestamp":" 946804191399"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804192860","data":{"timestamp":" 946804192859"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804194648","data":{"timestamp":" 946804194648"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804197800","data":{"timestamp":" 946804197800"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804199327","data":{"timestamp":" 946804199326"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804202407","data":{"timestamp":" 946804202406"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" WALIMWONEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804204148","data":{"timestamp":" 946804204148"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804205876","data":{"timestamp":" 946804205876"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804210643","data":{"timestamp":" 946804210643"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804211781","data":{"timestamp":" 946804211781"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804214087","data":{"timestamp":" 946804214086"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804215853","data":{"timestamp":" 946804215853"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804217942","data":{"timestamp":" 946804217941"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804218229","data":{"timestamp":" 946804218229"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804222733","data":{"timestamp":" 946804222733"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804224068","data":{"timestamp":" 946804224067"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804225219","data":{"timestamp":" 946804225219"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804226954","data":{"timestamp":" 946804226954"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804228821","data":{"timestamp":" 946804228821"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804229104","data":{"timestamp":" 946804229103"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804230217","data":{"timestamp":" 946804230217"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804231113","data":{"timestamp":" 946804231113"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" HURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804233015","data":{"timestamp":" 946804233015"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804234020","data":{"timestamp":" 946804234020"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804234125","data":{"timestamp":" 946804234124"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804247726","data":{"timestamp":" 946804247726"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804257866","data":{"timestamp":" 946804257866"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804263361","data":{"timestamp":" 946804263360"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804270672","data":{"timestamp":" 946804270672"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804278858","data":{"timestamp":" 946804278858"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.cap.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804288589","data":{"timestamp":" 946804288589"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a1335738-1a94-4db3-939e-4c903305aeed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804297352","data":{"timestamp":" 946804297352"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804297575","data":{"timestamp":" 946804297575"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804298538","data":{"timestamp":" 946804298538"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804299816","data":{"timestamp":" 946804299816"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804302680","data":{"timestamp":" 946804302680"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804303527","data":{"timestamp":" 946804303527"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804303840","data":{"timestamp":" 946804303840"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804305083","data":{"timestamp":" 946804305083"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804306008","data":{"timestamp":" 946804306008"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804306064","data":{"timestamp":" 946804306064"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804319300","data":{"timestamp":" 946804319300"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804327460","data":{"timestamp":" 946804327460"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 9c043911-0115-4f06-96db-859418d9a0fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804339091","data":{"timestamp":" 946804339091"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804340713","data":{"timestamp":" 946804340713"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804342629","data":{"timestamp":" 946804342629"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804344400","data":{"timestamp":" 946804344400"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804346530","data":{"timestamp":" 946804346530"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804348383","data":{"timestamp":" 946804348383"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804352412","data":{"timestamp":" 946804352412"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804353474","data":{"timestamp":" 946804353474"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804358202","data":{"timestamp":" 946804358202"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804359589","data":{"timestamp":" 946804359588"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804359753","data":{"timestamp":" 946804359753"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804360682","data":{"timestamp":" 946804360682"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804361913","data":{"timestamp":" 946804361913"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804363676","data":{"timestamp":" 946804363676"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804365205","data":{"timestamp":" 946804365205"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804366692","data":{"timestamp":" 946804366692"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804367108","data":{"timestamp":" 946804367108"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804370976","data":{"timestamp":" 946804370976"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" START_HAKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804372407","data":{"timestamp":" 946804372407"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804374903","data":{"timestamp":" 946804374903"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804379100","data":{"timestamp":" 946804379100"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804380705","data":{"timestamp":" 946804380705"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAHITAJI"," userResponse":" START_NAHITAJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804387557","data":{"timestamp":" 946804387556"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAHITAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804391448","data":{"timestamp":" 946804391448"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TONE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804394507","data":{"timestamp":" 946804394507"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804394784","data":{"timestamp":" 946804394784"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804398320","data":{"timestamp":" 946804398320"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804400138","data":{"timestamp":" 946804400138"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804402172","data":{"timestamp":" 946804402172"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINATOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804404156","data":{"timestamp":" 946804404155"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804405717","data":{"timestamp":" 946804405717"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804405812","data":{"timestamp":" 946804405812"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804411059","data":{"timestamp":" 946804411059"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804420011","data":{"timestamp":" 946804420010"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804427279","data":{"timestamp":" 946804427279"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804433844","data":{"timestamp":" 946804433844"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804439839","data":{"timestamp":" 946804439838"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" a8e2473f-ebb6-4067-816a-6d0e156198f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804450656","data":{"timestamp":" 946804450656"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804452891","data":{"timestamp":" 946804452891"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804455133","data":{"timestamp":" 946804455133"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804457058","data":{"timestamp":" 946804457057"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804458821","data":{"timestamp":" 946804458821"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804462491","data":{"timestamp":" 946804462491"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804464879","data":{"timestamp":" 946804464879"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804468725","data":{"timestamp":" 946804468725"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804469900","data":{"timestamp":" 946804469900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804471099","data":{"timestamp":" 946804471099"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804473373","data":{"timestamp":" 946804473373"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804475301","data":{"timestamp":" 946804475301"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804477518","data":{"timestamp":" 946804477518"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804479593","data":{"timestamp":" 946804479593"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPENZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804481597","data":{"timestamp":" 946804481597"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804485344","data":{"timestamp":" 946804485344"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" START_ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804487514","data":{"timestamp":" 946804487514"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804489769","data":{"timestamp":" 946804489768"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804489890","data":{"timestamp":" 946804489890"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804495366","data":{"timestamp":" 946804495365"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804500495","data":{"timestamp":" 946804500495"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804506473","data":{"timestamp":" 946804506473"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804525253","data":{"timestamp":" 946804525253"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804532311","data":{"timestamp":" 946804532310"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 601b4908-3a6c-46b0-89a7-ae7884fe3184"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804542857","data":{"timestamp":" 946804542857"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804544910","data":{"timestamp":" 946804544910"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804548673","data":{"timestamp":" 946804548673"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804550624","data":{"timestamp":" 946804550624"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804553010","data":{"timestamp":" 946804553010"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804555240","data":{"timestamp":" 946804555240"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804557468","data":{"timestamp":" 946804557468"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804559047","data":{"timestamp":" 946804559047"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804561256","data":{"timestamp":" 946804561256"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804563822","data":{"timestamp":" 946804563822"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804565448","data":{"timestamp":" 946804565448"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804567216","data":{"timestamp":" 946804567216"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804569662","data":{"timestamp":" 946804569662"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804570213","data":{"timestamp":" 946804570213"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804571275","data":{"timestamp":" 946804571275"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" ILITOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804573700","data":{"timestamp":" 946804573700"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804575634","data":{"timestamp":" 946804575634"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804577295","data":{"timestamp":" 946804577295"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804577669","data":{"timestamp":" 946804577669"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804579262","data":{"timestamp":" 946804579262"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804580537","data":{"timestamp":" 946804580536"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804580652","data":{"timestamp":" 946804580652"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804585973","data":{"timestamp":" 946804585971"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 3751d27e-4610-4e27-b64b-ac5caef264c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804597758","data":{"timestamp":" 946804597758"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804597895","data":{"timestamp":" 946804597894"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804598040","data":{"timestamp":" 946804598039"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804602952","data":{"timestamp":" 946804602951"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804607908","data":{"timestamp":" 946804607907"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804614293","data":{"timestamp":" 946804614293"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804620144","data":{"timestamp":" 946804620144"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804626021","data":{"timestamp":" 946804626021"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804636476","data":{"timestamp":" 946804636476"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804641776","data":{"timestamp":" 946804641776"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804649066","data":{"timestamp":" 946804649066"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804653822","data":{"timestamp":" 946804653821"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804660718","data":{"timestamp":" 946804660718"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804666789","data":{"timestamp":" 946804666788"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804673805","data":{"timestamp":" 946804673804"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804680522","data":{"timestamp":" 946804680522"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804689457","data":{"timestamp":" 946804689457"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804695700","data":{"timestamp":" 946804695699"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804704200","data":{"timestamp":" 946804704200"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804710622","data":{"timestamp":" 946804710621"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804715998","data":{"timestamp":" 946804715998"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804722061","data":{"timestamp":" 946804722060"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804731777","data":{"timestamp":" 946804731777"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804737328","data":{"timestamp":" 946804737328"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804742462","data":{"timestamp":" 946804742461"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804747754","data":{"timestamp":" 946804747753"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804754207","data":{"timestamp":" 946804754207"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804760534","data":{"timestamp":" 946804760534"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804765555","data":{"timestamp":" 946804765553"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804770930","data":{"timestamp":" 946804770930"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804782192","data":{"timestamp":" 946804782191"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804796636","data":{"timestamp":" 946804796636"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804806174","data":{"timestamp":" 946804806174"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804812357","data":{"timestamp":" 946804812357"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804823302","data":{"timestamp":" 946804823301"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804830015","data":{"timestamp":" 946804830014"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 106b565f-5736-426d-92ad-00c263274756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804845891","data":{"timestamp":" 946804845891"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804847302","data":{"timestamp":" 946804847302"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804849662","data":{"timestamp":" 946804849662"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804851097","data":{"timestamp":" 946804851097"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804852857","data":{"timestamp":" 946804852857"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804854856","data":{"timestamp":" 946804854856"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804856909","data":{"timestamp":" 946804856909"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804859023","data":{"timestamp":" 946804859022"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804861261","data":{"timestamp":" 946804861261"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804863552","data":{"timestamp":" 946804863551"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804865520","data":{"timestamp":" 946804865519"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804867228","data":{"timestamp":" 946804867228"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804882295","data":{"timestamp":" 946804882295"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804885868","data":{"timestamp":" 946804885868"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804888384","data":{"timestamp":" 946804888384"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804890118","data":{"timestamp":" 946804890118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804892406","data":{"timestamp":" 946804892406"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804894113","data":{"timestamp":" 946804894113"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804896371","data":{"timestamp":" 946804896371"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804898220","data":{"timestamp":" 946804898220"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804899998","data":{"timestamp":" 946804899998"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804902460","data":{"timestamp":" 946804902460"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804904529","data":{"timestamp":" 946804904529"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804906689","data":{"timestamp":" 946804906689"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804908594","data":{"timestamp":" 946804908594"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BONDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804910118","data":{"timestamp":" 946804910118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804912449","data":{"timestamp":" 946804912449"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINGILO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804914395","data":{"timestamp":" 946804914395"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804916546","data":{"timestamp":" 946804916546"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804918841","data":{"timestamp":" 946804918841"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804920907","data":{"timestamp":" 946804920907"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804922835","data":{"timestamp":" 946804922834"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804924829","data":{"timestamp":" 946804924829"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804926846","data":{"timestamp":" 946804926846"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804928478","data":{"timestamp":" 946804928478"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804930304","data":{"timestamp":" 946804930304"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804932064","data":{"timestamp":" 946804932064"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804934034","data":{"timestamp":" 946804934033"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804935782","data":{"timestamp":" 946804935781"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804937528","data":{"timestamp":" 946804937528"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804939623","data":{"timestamp":" 946804939623"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" START_WALICHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804941688","data":{"timestamp":" 946804941688"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804943900","data":{"timestamp":" 946804943900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804945907","data":{"timestamp":" 946804945907"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804947744","data":{"timestamp":" 946804947744"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804949704","data":{"timestamp":" 946804949704"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804951818","data":{"timestamp":" 946804951818"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804954034","data":{"timestamp":" 946804954034"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804955716","data":{"timestamp":" 946804955716"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804957684","data":{"timestamp":" 946804957683"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804959187","data":{"timestamp":" 946804959187"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804960952","data":{"timestamp":" 946804960952"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804962685","data":{"timestamp":" 946804962684"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804964105","data":{"timestamp":" 946804964104"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804966420","data":{"timestamp":" 946804966419"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOCHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804970418","data":{"timestamp":" 946804970418"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804972847","data":{"timestamp":" 946804972847"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804974819","data":{"timestamp":" 946804974819"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804976693","data":{"timestamp":" 946804976693"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804978573","data":{"timestamp":" 946804978573"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804980682","data":{"timestamp":" 946804980682"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804982705","data":{"timestamp":" 946804982705"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804985457","data":{"timestamp":" 946804985457"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIMKASIRISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804987829","data":{"timestamp":" 946804987828"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804989632","data":{"timestamp":" 946804989632"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804994653","data":{"timestamp":" 946804994653"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804996136","data":{"timestamp":" 946804996136"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946804998236","data":{"timestamp":" 946804998236"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805000335","data":{"timestamp":" 946805000335"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805002111","data":{"timestamp":" 946805002111"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805003854","data":{"timestamp":" 946805003854"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805007724","data":{"timestamp":" 946805007724"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINACHOKUWEZESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805011991","data":{"timestamp":" 946805011991"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805016038","data":{"timestamp":" 946805016038"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGIZAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805017668","data":{"timestamp":" 946805017668"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805020062","data":{"timestamp":" 946805020061"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAARUFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805023475","data":{"timestamp":" 946805023474"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805024354","data":{"timestamp":" 946805024354"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805025546","data":{"timestamp":" 946805025546"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805026543","data":{"timestamp":" 946805026543"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805027904","data":{"timestamp":" 946805027904"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" KINACHOKUWEZESHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805030123","data":{"timestamp":" 946805030123"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805031954","data":{"timestamp":" 946805031954"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805033681","data":{"timestamp":" 946805033680"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805035825","data":{"timestamp":" 946805035825"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINENE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805038052","data":{"timestamp":" 946805038052"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805041629","data":{"timestamp":" 946805041629"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805044132","data":{"timestamp":" 946805044132"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805047621","data":{"timestamp":" 946805047620"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805050284","data":{"timestamp":" 946805050283"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDEKEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805052198","data":{"timestamp":" 946805052198"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805053938","data":{"timestamp":" 946805053937"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805056134","data":{"timestamp":" 946805056134"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHINDANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805057792","data":{"timestamp":" 946805057792"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805059776","data":{"timestamp":" 946805059776"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805061764","data":{"timestamp":" 946805061764"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805064294","data":{"timestamp":" 946805064293"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805066587","data":{"timestamp":" 946805066587"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805069008","data":{"timestamp":" 946805069008"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805070805","data":{"timestamp":" 946805070805"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805078219","data":{"timestamp":" 946805078219"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805079899","data":{"timestamp":" 946805079898"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805080271","data":{"timestamp":" 946805080271"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805085751","data":{"timestamp":" 946805085750"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805100769","data":{"timestamp":" 946805100768"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805106605","data":{"timestamp":" 946805106605"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805129904","data":{"timestamp":" 946805129904"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805144718","data":{"timestamp":" 946805144718"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" dfd13503-c253-4a08-a47a-900055137f97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805156720","data":{"timestamp":" 946805156720"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805159380","data":{"timestamp":" 946805159380"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805159525","data":{"timestamp":" 946805159525"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805166269","data":{"timestamp":" 946805166268"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805173303","data":{"timestamp":" 946805173303"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805179972","data":{"timestamp":" 946805179972"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805186649","data":{"timestamp":" 946805186649"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805192039","data":{"timestamp":" 946805192038"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805198364","data":{"timestamp":" 946805198364"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805207411","data":{"timestamp":" 946805207411"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 72c3a42b-2624-4c6d-bff8-858691036d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805222842","data":{"timestamp":" 946805222842"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805225135","data":{"timestamp":" 946805225135"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805227771","data":{"timestamp":" 946805227771"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805229548","data":{"timestamp":" 946805229548"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805231322","data":{"timestamp":" 946805231321"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805233332","data":{"timestamp":" 946805233331"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805235608","data":{"timestamp":" 946805235608"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805237306","data":{"timestamp":" 946805237306"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805238979","data":{"timestamp":" 946805238979"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805248184","data":{"timestamp":" 946805248184"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEOGOPWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805251573","data":{"timestamp":" 946805251573"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805253666","data":{"timestamp":" 946805253666"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805255470","data":{"timestamp":" 946805255470"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805257817","data":{"timestamp":" 946805257817"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805259961","data":{"timestamp":" 946805259960"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASHIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805262179","data":{"timestamp":" 946805262179"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805263673","data":{"timestamp":" 946805263673"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805265706","data":{"timestamp":" 946805265706"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805267336","data":{"timestamp":" 946805267336"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805271080","data":{"timestamp":" 946805271080"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805273278","data":{"timestamp":" 946805273277"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805275569","data":{"timestamp":" 946805275569"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805276820","data":{"timestamp":" 946805276820"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805279098","data":{"timestamp":" 946805279098"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805282496","data":{"timestamp":" 946805282495"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805285231","data":{"timestamp":" 946805285231"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805287112","data":{"timestamp":" 946805287112"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805289208","data":{"timestamp":" 946805289208"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805291472","data":{"timestamp":" 946805291472"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805293266","data":{"timestamp":" 946805293266"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805295093","data":{"timestamp":" 946805295093"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805298327","data":{"timestamp":" 946805298327"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805301427","data":{"timestamp":" 946805301426"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805303663","data":{"timestamp":" 946805303663"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805305238","data":{"timestamp":" 946805305237"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805306973","data":{"timestamp":" 946805306973"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805309093","data":{"timestamp":" 946805309093"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805310854","data":{"timestamp":" 946805310854"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805312798","data":{"timestamp":" 946805312798"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805314879","data":{"timestamp":" 946805314879"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805316723","data":{"timestamp":" 946805316723"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805318761","data":{"timestamp":" 946805318760"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805320913","data":{"timestamp":" 946805320913"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805323207","data":{"timestamp":" 946805323207"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJINASUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805325152","data":{"timestamp":" 946805325152"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805327652","data":{"timestamp":" 946805327651"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805329554","data":{"timestamp":" 946805329553"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805331533","data":{"timestamp":" 946805331533"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULINASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805333599","data":{"timestamp":" 946805333599"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805335411","data":{"timestamp":" 946805335411"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805337427","data":{"timestamp":" 946805337427"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805339452","data":{"timestamp":" 946805339452"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805341048","data":{"timestamp":" 946805341048"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805343219","data":{"timestamp":" 946805343219"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805345459","data":{"timestamp":" 946805345459"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805347553","data":{"timestamp":" 946805347553"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805349214","data":{"timestamp":" 946805349214"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805351223","data":{"timestamp":" 946805351223"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805353031","data":{"timestamp":" 946805353031"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805355174","data":{"timestamp":" 946805355174"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805357538","data":{"timestamp":" 946805357538"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805359602","data":{"timestamp":" 946805359602"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805361922","data":{"timestamp":" 946805361922"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805364026","data":{"timestamp":" 946805364026"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805365683","data":{"timestamp":" 946805365683"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805367519","data":{"timestamp":" 946805367519"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805369589","data":{"timestamp":" 946805369589"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOMWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805371684","data":{"timestamp":" 946805371684"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805373499","data":{"timestamp":" 946805373499"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805375669","data":{"timestamp":" 946805375669"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805377415","data":{"timestamp":" 946805377414"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805379391","data":{"timestamp":" 946805379391"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805381147","data":{"timestamp":" 946805381147"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805382850","data":{"timestamp":" 946805382849"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805384497","data":{"timestamp":" 946805384497"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805387011","data":{"timestamp":" 946805387011"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805388871","data":{"timestamp":" 946805388871"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805391028","data":{"timestamp":" 946805391028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805393564","data":{"timestamp":" 946805393564"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805396363","data":{"timestamp":" 946805396363"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805398433","data":{"timestamp":" 946805398433"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYONGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805400309","data":{"timestamp":" 946805400309"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805402166","data":{"timestamp":" 946805402166"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805404320","data":{"timestamp":" 946805404320"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805407452","data":{"timestamp":" 946805407452"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805409316","data":{"timestamp":" 946805409316"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805411241","data":{"timestamp":" 946805411241"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805413384","data":{"timestamp":" 946805413384"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805415166","data":{"timestamp":" 946805415166"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805416942","data":{"timestamp":" 946805416941"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805418962","data":{"timestamp":" 946805418962"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805420841","data":{"timestamp":" 946805420840"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805422882","data":{"timestamp":" 946805422882"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805426365","data":{"timestamp":" 946805426365"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805426994","data":{"timestamp":" 946805426994"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805430196","data":{"timestamp":" 946805430196"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805432630","data":{"timestamp":" 946805432630"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805434972","data":{"timestamp":" 946805434972"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805437264","data":{"timestamp":" 946805437264"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805439466","data":{"timestamp":" 946805439466"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805442040","data":{"timestamp":" 946805442039"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKILIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805443810","data":{"timestamp":" 946805443810"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805446515","data":{"timestamp":" 946805446515"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUNGUZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805448061","data":{"timestamp":" 946805448061"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805450111","data":{"timestamp":" 946805450111"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805452348","data":{"timestamp":" 946805452348"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805454342","data":{"timestamp":" 946805454342"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805456816","data":{"timestamp":" 946805456816"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805458572","data":{"timestamp":" 946805458572"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805460774","data":{"timestamp":" 946805460774"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKWEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805462925","data":{"timestamp":" 946805462925"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805465476","data":{"timestamp":" 946805465476"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805468743","data":{"timestamp":" 946805468743"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805470564","data":{"timestamp":" 946805470564"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805472555","data":{"timestamp":" 946805472555"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805474781","data":{"timestamp":" 946805474781"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805476377","data":{"timestamp":" 946805476377"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805478365","data":{"timestamp":" 946805478365"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805480478","data":{"timestamp":" 946805480478"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805482449","data":{"timestamp":" 946805482449"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805484698","data":{"timestamp":" 946805484698"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805486828","data":{"timestamp":" 946805486828"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805489214","data":{"timestamp":" 946805489214"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805491061","data":{"timestamp":" 946805491060"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805493541","data":{"timestamp":" 946805493541"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805495695","data":{"timestamp":" 946805495695"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOPENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805497368","data":{"timestamp":" 946805497368"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805499185","data":{"timestamp":" 946805499185"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805501182","data":{"timestamp":" 946805501182"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805502901","data":{"timestamp":" 946805502901"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805504722","data":{"timestamp":" 946805504722"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805506351","data":{"timestamp":" 946805506351"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805511329","data":{"timestamp":" 946805511329"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805513695","data":{"timestamp":" 946805513695"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805515976","data":{"timestamp":" 946805515976"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805517814","data":{"timestamp":" 946805517814"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805519847","data":{"timestamp":" 946805519846"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805521979","data":{"timestamp":" 946805521979"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805524360","data":{"timestamp":" 946805524360"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805526365","data":{"timestamp":" 946805526365"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIOKOE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805528339","data":{"timestamp":" 946805528339"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805530075","data":{"timestamp":" 946805530075"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805531935","data":{"timestamp":" 946805531934"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805533754","data":{"timestamp":" 946805533753"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805536073","data":{"timestamp":" 946805536073"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805537943","data":{"timestamp":" 946805537942"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kamwe Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805540345","data":{"timestamp":" 946805540345"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kamwe Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805542526","data":{"timestamp":" 946805542526"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kamwe Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805544259","data":{"timestamp":" 946805544259"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805545923","data":{"timestamp":" 946805545923"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805547723","data":{"timestamp":" 946805547723"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805549645","data":{"timestamp":" 946805549645"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKATILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805552321","data":{"timestamp":" 946805552321"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIKUOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805554479","data":{"timestamp":" 946805554479"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805556563","data":{"timestamp":" 946805556563"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805558375","data":{"timestamp":" 946805558375"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805560456","data":{"timestamp":" 946805560456"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805562222","data":{"timestamp":" 946805562222"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805564207","data":{"timestamp":" 946805564207"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805569078","data":{"timestamp":" 946805569078"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805571002","data":{"timestamp":" 946805571001"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805574099","data":{"timestamp":" 946805574099"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAHIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805575794","data":{"timestamp":" 946805575793"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805578077","data":{"timestamp":" 946805578077"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITATENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805579768","data":{"timestamp":" 946805579768"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805582122","data":{"timestamp":" 946805582122"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805584469","data":{"timestamp":" 946805584469"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805586307","data":{"timestamp":" 946805586307"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805588843","data":{"timestamp":" 946805588843"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805591169","data":{"timestamp":" 946805591169"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805593737","data":{"timestamp":" 946805593737"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805597925","data":{"timestamp":" 946805597924"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANIOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805599649","data":{"timestamp":" 946805599649"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805602016","data":{"timestamp":" 946805602015"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805603909","data":{"timestamp":" 946805603909"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwonea Simba huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805605991","data":{"timestamp":" 946805605991"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwonea Simba huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805607737","data":{"timestamp":" 946805607737"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwonea Simba huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805609987","data":{"timestamp":" 946805609987"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwonea Simba huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805612486","data":{"timestamp":" 946805612486"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIPENDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805614348","data":{"timestamp":" 946805614347"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805616065","data":{"timestamp":" 946805616065"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805618041","data":{"timestamp":" 946805618041"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805619844","data":{"timestamp":" 946805619844"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805621708","data":{"timestamp":" 946805621708"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805623406","data":{"timestamp":" 946805623406"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805625431","data":{"timestamp":" 946805625431"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805627071","data":{"timestamp":" 946805627071"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805628691","data":{"timestamp":" 946805628691"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805630472","data":{"timestamp":" 946805630472"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805632273","data":{"timestamp":" 946805632273"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805634517","data":{"timestamp":" 946805634516"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805637124","data":{"timestamp":" 946805637124"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUMIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805638679","data":{"timestamp":" 946805638679"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805640658","data":{"timestamp":" 946805640658"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805642801","data":{"timestamp":" 946805642801"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805644582","data":{"timestamp":" 946805644582"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805646539","data":{"timestamp":" 946805646538"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805650319","data":{"timestamp":" 946805650319"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805652149","data":{"timestamp":" 946805652149"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805654389","data":{"timestamp":" 946805654388"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwokoa rafikiye mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805656898","data":{"timestamp":" 946805656898"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwokoa rafikiye mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805659449","data":{"timestamp":" 946805659449"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwokoa rafikiye mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805661043","data":{"timestamp":" 946805661043"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwokoa rafikiye mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805663078","data":{"timestamp":" 946805663078"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASANTE"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805667743","data":{"timestamp":" 946805667743"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASANTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805669417","data":{"timestamp":" 946805669417"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805671648","data":{"timestamp":" 946805671648"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805673672","data":{"timestamp":" 946805673672"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805675590","data":{"timestamp":" 946805675590"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805677571","data":{"timestamp":" 946805677571"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805679496","data":{"timestamp":" 946805679495"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805681459","data":{"timestamp":" 946805681459"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805683241","data":{"timestamp":" 946805683241"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805685373","data":{"timestamp":" 946805685373"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805687866","data":{"timestamp":" 946805687866"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805691499","data":{"timestamp":" 946805691499"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805693068","data":{"timestamp":" 946805693068"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805695758","data":{"timestamp":" 946805695758"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805697671","data":{"timestamp":" 946805697671"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805699708","data":{"timestamp":" 946805699708"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805701384","data":{"timestamp":" 946805701384"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805704104","data":{"timestamp":" 946805704104"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805706506","data":{"timestamp":" 946805706506"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805708721","data":{"timestamp":" 946805708721"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805710903","data":{"timestamp":" 946805710903"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805712987","data":{"timestamp":" 946805712986"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805715218","data":{"timestamp":" 946805715218"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805717250","data":{"timestamp":" 946805717250"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805719997","data":{"timestamp":" 946805719997"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805722786","data":{"timestamp":" 946805722785"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805724991","data":{"timestamp":" 946805724991"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805728003","data":{"timestamp":" 946805728003"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805730425","data":{"timestamp":" 946805730424"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805731192","data":{"timestamp":" 946805731192"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805734464","data":{"timestamp":" 946805734463"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805737751","data":{"timestamp":" 946805737751"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805740179","data":{"timestamp":" 946805740179"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805742122","data":{"timestamp":" 946805742122"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805744656","data":{"timestamp":" 946805744656"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAITAKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805746581","data":{"timestamp":" 946805746581"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOROKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805748445","data":{"timestamp":" 946805748445"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805750193","data":{"timestamp":" 946805750193"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805752231","data":{"timestamp":" 946805752231"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805759075","data":{"timestamp":" 946805759075"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805763468","data":{"timestamp":" 946805763468"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805765736","data":{"timestamp":" 946805765736"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805768267","data":{"timestamp":" 946805768267"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKICHECHEMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805770093","data":{"timestamp":" 946805770093"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805771727","data":{"timestamp":" 946805771727"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805775254","data":{"timestamp":" 946805775253"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYONGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805777486","data":{"timestamp":" 946805777486"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805779383","data":{"timestamp":" 946805779383"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805782194","data":{"timestamp":" 946805782194"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805784084","data":{"timestamp":" 946805784084"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805789189","data":{"timestamp":" 946805789189"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805790400","data":{"timestamp":" 946805790400"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" START_AKICHECHEMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805791770","data":{"timestamp":" 946805791770"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805793690","data":{"timestamp":" 946805793690"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805797545","data":{"timestamp":" 946805797545"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWAONA"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805799523","data":{"timestamp":" 946805799523"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWAONA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805801553","data":{"timestamp":" 946805801552"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805803242","data":{"timestamp":" 946805803242"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805804697","data":{"timestamp":" 946805804697"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805805363","data":{"timestamp":" 946805805363"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" NGIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805807056","data":{"timestamp":" 946805807056"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805808218","data":{"timestamp":" 946805808218"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805809801","data":{"timestamp":" 946805809801"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" UNYONGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805811377","data":{"timestamp":" 946805811377"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805814473","data":{"timestamp":" 946805814473"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805816466","data":{"timestamp":" 946805816466"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOPENI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805818309","data":{"timestamp":" 946805818309"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805820276","data":{"timestamp":" 946805820276"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOPENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805822646","data":{"timestamp":" 946805822646"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805824420","data":{"timestamp":" 946805824420"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805826098","data":{"timestamp":" 946805826098"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805827937","data":{"timestamp":" 946805827937"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805829656","data":{"timestamp":" 946805829656"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805831926","data":{"timestamp":" 946805831926"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805835422","data":{"timestamp":" 946805835422"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805837660","data":{"timestamp":" 946805837660"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805839994","data":{"timestamp":" 946805839993"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805841646","data":{"timestamp":" 946805841646"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805843669","data":{"timestamp":" 946805843669"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805849974","data":{"timestamp":" 946805849974"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805852321","data":{"timestamp":" 946805852321"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805854218","data":{"timestamp":" 946805854217"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805855891","data":{"timestamp":" 946805855891"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805857862","data":{"timestamp":" 946805857862"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805859965","data":{"timestamp":" 946805859965"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805862208","data":{"timestamp":" 946805862208"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMENASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805864306","data":{"timestamp":" 946805864306"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805866200","data":{"timestamp":" 946805866200"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805867947","data":{"timestamp":" 946805867946"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805871407","data":{"timestamp":" 946805871407"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805874980","data":{"timestamp":" 946805874979"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805878131","data":{"timestamp":" 946805878130"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805881008","data":{"timestamp":" 946805881008"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805881667","data":{"timestamp":" 946805881667"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805883978","data":{"timestamp":" 946805883978"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805886007","data":{"timestamp":" 946805886007"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805890100","data":{"timestamp":" 946805890099"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805891199","data":{"timestamp":" 946805891198"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" START_TAFADHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805893984","data":{"timestamp":" 946805893983"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805896436","data":{"timestamp":" 946805896436"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805900186","data":{"timestamp":" 946805900186"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIPATIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805903049","data":{"timestamp":" 946805903049"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805904747","data":{"timestamp":" 946805904747"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805907014","data":{"timestamp":" 946805907014"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805908980","data":{"timestamp":" 946805908980"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805910711","data":{"timestamp":" 946805910711"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805913231","data":{"timestamp":" 946805913231"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805915539","data":{"timestamp":" 946805915539"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805917337","data":{"timestamp":" 946805917337"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805919458","data":{"timestamp":" 946805919458"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alishtuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805921522","data":{"timestamp":" 946805921522"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alishtuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHTUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805924560","data":{"timestamp":" 946805924560"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805926526","data":{"timestamp":" 946805926526"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805929087","data":{"timestamp":" 946805929087"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805930831","data":{"timestamp":" 946805930831"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805933307","data":{"timestamp":" 946805933307"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805935248","data":{"timestamp":" 946805935248"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNATAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805938108","data":{"timestamp":" 946805938108"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805940277","data":{"timestamp":" 946805940277"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805942028","data":{"timestamp":" 946805942028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805947942","data":{"timestamp":" 946805947941"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKITIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805950218","data":{"timestamp":" 946805950218"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805955574","data":{"timestamp":" 946805955574"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805956557","data":{"timestamp":" 946805956557"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805957380","data":{"timestamp":" 946805957380"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" START_NINAKUFA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805958849","data":{"timestamp":" 946805958849"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805960306","data":{"timestamp":" 946805960306"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805962413","data":{"timestamp":" 946805962413"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805964262","data":{"timestamp":" 946805964262"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805966240","data":{"timestamp":" 946805966240"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAKUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805968193","data":{"timestamp":" 946805968193"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805969251","data":{"timestamp":" 946805969251"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWA"," userResponse":" START_INGAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805971824","data":{"timestamp":" 946805971824"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805973847","data":{"timestamp":" 946805973847"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805975503","data":{"timestamp":" 946805975503"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805978082","data":{"timestamp":" 946805978082"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYONGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805980229","data":{"timestamp":" 946805980229"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805982169","data":{"timestamp":" 946805982169"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805984336","data":{"timestamp":" 946805984336"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805986333","data":{"timestamp":" 946805986333"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805988171","data":{"timestamp":" 946805988171"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805990319","data":{"timestamp":" 946805990319"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805996369","data":{"timestamp":" 946805996369"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946805999034","data":{"timestamp":" 946805999034"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806001622","data":{"timestamp":" 946806001622"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806003539","data":{"timestamp":" 946806003539"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806005371","data":{"timestamp":" 946806005371"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806007866","data":{"timestamp":" 946806007865"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806009898","data":{"timestamp":" 946806009898"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONYESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806011842","data":{"timestamp":" 946806011842"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806014129","data":{"timestamp":" 946806014129"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806017238","data":{"timestamp":" 946806017237"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIPONIPATIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806019609","data":{"timestamp":" 946806019609"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806021352","data":{"timestamp":" 946806021352"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806025009","data":{"timestamp":" 946806025009"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806027020","data":{"timestamp":" 946806027020"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806029534","data":{"timestamp":" 946806029534"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806031993","data":{"timestamp":" 946806031993"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806034245","data":{"timestamp":" 946806034245"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806036830","data":{"timestamp":" 946806036830"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINGURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806040202","data":{"timestamp":" 946806040202"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806042701","data":{"timestamp":" 946806042701"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFAHAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806044489","data":{"timestamp":" 946806044489"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806046389","data":{"timestamp":" 946806046389"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806048531","data":{"timestamp":" 946806048531"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806050593","data":{"timestamp":" 946806050593"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806052451","data":{"timestamp":" 946806052451"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806054434","data":{"timestamp":" 946806054433"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806056353","data":{"timestamp":" 946806056352"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806058105","data":{"timestamp":" 946806058104"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806060397","data":{"timestamp":" 946806060397"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806060567","data":{"timestamp":" 946806060567"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806063873","data":{"timestamp":" 946806063873"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806065973","data":{"timestamp":" 946806065973"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806076398","data":{"timestamp":" 946806076397"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806078492","data":{"timestamp":" 946806078492"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sawa sawa Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806080478","data":{"timestamp":" 946806080478"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sawa sawa Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806082567","data":{"timestamp":" 946806082567"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sawa sawa Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806085471","data":{"timestamp":" 946806085471"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sawa sawa Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806087975","data":{"timestamp":" 946806087975"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUPATIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806090028","data":{"timestamp":" 946806090028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806091910","data":{"timestamp":" 946806091910"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806094058","data":{"timestamp":" 946806094058"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806097130","data":{"timestamp":" 946806097129"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806099084","data":{"timestamp":" 946806099084"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806101247","data":{"timestamp":" 946806101247"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806103332","data":{"timestamp":" 946806103331"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIONYESHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806105164","data":{"timestamp":" 946806105164"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806107448","data":{"timestamp":" 946806107448"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIVYONASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806109454","data":{"timestamp":" 946806109454"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806111645","data":{"timestamp":" 946806111645"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806114313","data":{"timestamp":" 946806114313"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAHITAJIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806116055","data":{"timestamp":" 946806116055"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806118352","data":{"timestamp":" 946806118352"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806120080","data":{"timestamp":" 946806120080"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806123141","data":{"timestamp":" 946806123141"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806124942","data":{"timestamp":" 946806124942"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806127180","data":{"timestamp":" 946806127180"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806129029","data":{"timestamp":" 946806129029"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" START_ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806131557","data":{"timestamp":" 946806131557"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806132985","data":{"timestamp":" 946806132985"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806138484","data":{"timestamp":" 946806138484"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806140608","data":{"timestamp":" 946806140608"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806142298","data":{"timestamp":" 946806142297"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806144991","data":{"timestamp":" 946806144991"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806147214","data":{"timestamp":" 946806147214"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806150467","data":{"timestamp":" 946806150467"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806152398","data":{"timestamp":" 946806152398"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806154481","data":{"timestamp":" 946806154481"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806156781","data":{"timestamp":" 946806156781"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusubiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806159348","data":{"timestamp":" 946806159348"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusubiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806161920","data":{"timestamp":" 946806161919"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806164068","data":{"timestamp":" 946806164068"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806166186","data":{"timestamp":" 946806166186"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806168336","data":{"timestamp":" 946806168336"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806170309","data":{"timestamp":" 946806170309"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806172402","data":{"timestamp":" 946806172402"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806174900","data":{"timestamp":" 946806174900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806177243","data":{"timestamp":" 946806177243"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806180434","data":{"timestamp":" 946806180434"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONYESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806182598","data":{"timestamp":" 946806182597"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806184778","data":{"timestamp":" 946806184778"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806186821","data":{"timestamp":" 946806186821"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806190709","data":{"timestamp":" 946806190709"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYONASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806194884","data":{"timestamp":" 946806194883"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMBIENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806197184","data":{"timestamp":" 946806197184"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMBILIENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806199070","data":{"timestamp":" 946806199070"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806201035","data":{"timestamp":" 946806201035"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806202954","data":{"timestamp":" 946806202954"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806205629","data":{"timestamp":" 946806205629"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806207614","data":{"timestamp":" 946806207614"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806209322","data":{"timestamp":" 946806209322"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806212044","data":{"timestamp":" 946806212044"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806213729","data":{"timestamp":" 946806213729"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806215885","data":{"timestamp":" 946806215885"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806218114","data":{"timestamp":" 946806218114"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INUENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806219951","data":{"timestamp":" 946806219951"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806222179","data":{"timestamp":" 946806222179"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806224513","data":{"timestamp":" 946806224513"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNAPOKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806226671","data":{"timestamp":" 946806226671"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806228601","data":{"timestamp":" 946806228601"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806230565","data":{"timestamp":" 946806230565"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806232482","data":{"timestamp":" 946806232482"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWAONE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806234968","data":{"timestamp":" 946806234968"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISISITIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806237209","data":{"timestamp":" 946806237209"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806239595","data":{"timestamp":" 946806239595"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806241323","data":{"timestamp":" 946806241323"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806244548","data":{"timestamp":" 946806244548"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806246764","data":{"timestamp":" 946806246764"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYOWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806249032","data":{"timestamp":" 946806249032"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806251518","data":{"timestamp":" 946806251518"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806257853","data":{"timestamp":" 946806257852"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806259905","data":{"timestamp":" 946806259905"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806262272","data":{"timestamp":" 946806262272"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806264262","data":{"timestamp":" 946806264262"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806266622","data":{"timestamp":" 946806266621"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806268514","data":{"timestamp":" 946806268514"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806270540","data":{"timestamp":" 946806270540"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806272581","data":{"timestamp":" 946806272581"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806275595","data":{"timestamp":" 946806275595"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806279307","data":{"timestamp":" 946806279306"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806281573","data":{"timestamp":" 946806281573"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806283534","data":{"timestamp":" 946806283533"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806289028","data":{"timestamp":" 946806289028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806291072","data":{"timestamp":" 946806291072"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806292712","data":{"timestamp":" 946806292712"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806294540","data":{"timestamp":" 946806294540"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806297334","data":{"timestamp":" 946806297334"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufanyia lolote utakalo ukiniokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFANYIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806299682","data":{"timestamp":" 946806299682"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufanyia lolote utakalo ukiniokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOLOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806301779","data":{"timestamp":" 946806301779"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufanyia lolote utakalo ukiniokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKALO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806304375","data":{"timestamp":" 946806304375"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufanyia lolote utakalo ukiniokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKINIOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806306050","data":{"timestamp":" 946806306050"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806308724","data":{"timestamp":" 946806308724"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITATHUBUTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806318833","data":{"timestamp":" 946806318833"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806321600","data":{"timestamp":" 946806321600"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806323873","data":{"timestamp":" 946806323873"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUONGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806325596","data":{"timestamp":" 946806325596"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SITAWAHI"," userResponse":" KUNASWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806326872","data":{"timestamp":" 946806326872"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SITAWAHI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806328757","data":{"timestamp":" 946806328756"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITAWAHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806329926","data":{"timestamp":" 946806329925"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUKWAMINI"," userResponse":" START_NGIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806332666","data":{"timestamp":" 946806332665"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKWAMINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806334619","data":{"timestamp":" 946806334619"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806337120","data":{"timestamp":" 946806337120"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806339444","data":{"timestamp":" 946806339444"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806341680","data":{"timestamp":" 946806341680"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAWAONYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806343657","data":{"timestamp":" 946806343657"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806345775","data":{"timestamp":" 946806345775"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806347715","data":{"timestamp":" 946806347715"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806349890","data":{"timestamp":" 946806349890"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806354369","data":{"timestamp":" 946806354369"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806356544","data":{"timestamp":" 946806356544"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806359318","data":{"timestamp":" 946806359318"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUEPUKE"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806361430","data":{"timestamp":" 946806361430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUEPUKE"," userResponse":" MJANJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806363169","data":{"timestamp":" 946806363169"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUEPUKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806365028","data":{"timestamp":" 946806365028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806367083","data":{"timestamp":" 946806367083"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806368844","data":{"timestamp":" 946806368844"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806370676","data":{"timestamp":" 946806370676"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806372668","data":{"timestamp":" 946806372667"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJANJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806374712","data":{"timestamp":" 946806374712"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806380275","data":{"timestamp":" 946806380275"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806382905","data":{"timestamp":" 946806382905"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806385131","data":{"timestamp":" 946806385131"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806387075","data":{"timestamp":" 946806387075"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806389401","data":{"timestamp":" 946806389401"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806391539","data":{"timestamp":" 946806391539"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806393875","data":{"timestamp":" 946806393875"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806395943","data":{"timestamp":" 946806395942"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806397691","data":{"timestamp":" 946806397690"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806399630","data":{"timestamp":" 946806399630"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806401713","data":{"timestamp":" 946806401713"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806403560","data":{"timestamp":" 946806403560"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806405531","data":{"timestamp":" 946806405531"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806407645","data":{"timestamp":" 946806407645"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806409920","data":{"timestamp":" 946806409920"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEINULIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806411707","data":{"timestamp":" 946806411707"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806413678","data":{"timestamp":" 946806413678"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806415606","data":{"timestamp":" 946806415606"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWAONE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806418349","data":{"timestamp":" 946806418349"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806420877","data":{"timestamp":" 946806420877"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806422627","data":{"timestamp":" 946806422627"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806424521","data":{"timestamp":" 946806424520"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806427486","data":{"timestamp":" 946806427486"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806431042","data":{"timestamp":" 946806431042"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806433085","data":{"timestamp":" 946806433085"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806435478","data":{"timestamp":" 946806435478"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806437605","data":{"timestamp":" 946806437605"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806439431","data":{"timestamp":" 946806439430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806441145","data":{"timestamp":" 946806441145"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806443223","data":{"timestamp":" 946806443223"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806445465","data":{"timestamp":" 946806445465"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806447740","data":{"timestamp":" 946806447740"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806449279","data":{"timestamp":" 946806449279"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806450946","data":{"timestamp":" 946806450946"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806452926","data":{"timestamp":" 946806452926"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806455978","data":{"timestamp":" 946806455978"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEINULIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806458225","data":{"timestamp":" 946806458225"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHAKIKISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806461827","data":{"timestamp":" 946806461826"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806463500","data":{"timestamp":" 946806463500"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806465045","data":{"timestamp":" 946806465045"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806467122","data":{"timestamp":" 946806467122"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806468864","data":{"timestamp":" 946806468864"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806470877","data":{"timestamp":" 946806470877"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806471073","data":{"timestamp":" 946806471073"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806476021","data":{"timestamp":" 946806476020"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806481329","data":{"timestamp":" 946806481329"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806486685","data":{"timestamp":" 946806486684"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806494259","data":{"timestamp":" 946806494258"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806500001","data":{"timestamp":" 946806499998"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_75","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806506447","data":{"timestamp":" 946806506446"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806512338","data":{"timestamp":" 946806512338"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806519701","data":{"timestamp":" 946806519700"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806525436","data":{"timestamp":" 946806525436"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806531479","data":{"timestamp":" 946806531479"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806537285","data":{"timestamp":" 946806537284"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806559484","data":{"timestamp":" 946806559484"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806575726","data":{"timestamp":" 946806575725"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806581369","data":{"timestamp":" 946806581368"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806596242","data":{"timestamp":" 946806596242"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806606630","data":{"timestamp":" 946806606629"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806620097","data":{"timestamp":" 946806620096"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806628623","data":{"timestamp":" 946806628622"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" c9c12eba-19e0-4c5d-9d99-bcea8ae55f5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806638639","data":{"timestamp":" 946806638639"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806638864","data":{"timestamp":" 946806638864"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806639827","data":{"timestamp":" 946806639827"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806641101","data":{"timestamp":" 946806641101"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806644005","data":{"timestamp":" 946806644005"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806644849","data":{"timestamp":" 946806644849"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806645163","data":{"timestamp":" 946806645163"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806646397","data":{"timestamp":" 946806646397"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806649950","data":{"timestamp":" 946806649950"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806650934","data":{"timestamp":" 946806650934"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806651188","data":{"timestamp":" 946806651188"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806652133","data":{"timestamp":" 946806652133"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806664718","data":{"timestamp":" 946806664718"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806664741","data":{"timestamp":" 946806664740"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806664954","data":{"timestamp":" 946806664954"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806679151","data":{"timestamp":" 946806679151"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 559faee3-1f66-4718-8331-d6c5e5431bfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806690751","data":{"timestamp":" 946806690751"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 39c3ecfa-252b-4de8-b4e4-db0af4044cd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806704948","data":{"timestamp":" 946806704948"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 39c3ecfa-252b-4de8-b4e4-db0af4044cd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806704954","data":{"timestamp":" 946806704954"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 39c3ecfa-252b-4de8-b4e4-db0af4044cd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" STARTWRITING"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806718090","data":{"timestamp":" 946806718090"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 39c3ecfa-252b-4de8-b4e4-db0af4044cd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806724870","data":{"timestamp":" 946806724870"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 39c3ecfa-252b-4de8-b4e4-db0af4044cd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806729016","data":{"timestamp":" 946806729015"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 39c3ecfa-252b-4de8-b4e4-db0af4044cd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806731942","data":{"timestamp":" 946806731942"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 39c3ecfa-252b-4de8-b4e4-db0af4044cd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806732175","data":{"timestamp":" 946806732175"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_115459"," gameId":" 39c3ecfa-252b-4de8-b4e4-db0af4044cd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"end":"end"}]}